## **MUHAMAD ALFITO SANTOSA**

+6287899597978 | alfitosantosa@gmail.com Portfolio: https://alfitosans.github.io/lordsansPortfolio/ |LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lorddsans

## **SUMMARY**

Currently a second-year student majoring in Computer Science at Gunadarma University. I have 1 year experience in Gunadarma laboratory as lab assistant. I have a strong understanding in tech. I have a huge desire to learn new things. I have an interest in Building Design UI/UX Responsibility Web and Design UI/UX Responsibility Mobile related areas which will utilize my analytical and technical skills I've developed.

## **EDUCATION**

Sept 2020 – Present GUNADARMA UNIVERSITY

Depok, Indonesia

Bachelor of Computer Science, Expected Graduate September 2024 •

GPA: 3.52 / 4.0;.

Relevant Coursework: Web Development, Human-Computer Interaction, Software Engineering.

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Sept 2019 Responsive Web

Bogor, Indonesia

**Front-End and Back-End Engineer** a website that can be accessed with various devices that can be used without having to change its appearance, as a Front-End and Back-End Engineer my responsibilities are to:

- Programming all Responsive Web component in HTML, CSS and JavaScript language.
- Checking and fixing all bugs in program.

#### ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sept 2021 – Feb 2022 Fajrul Islam Gunadarma

Depok, Indonesia

Broadcast (Syi'ar & Dakwah)

Fajrul Islam Gunadarma is social organization that running in humanity and social activation, as a part of Broadcast on Fajrul Islam Gunadarma my responsibilities are to:

- Filtering information in community.
- Collaborated with over 100 members of Fajrul Islam Gunadarma.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## Sept 2021 – Sept 2022 Lembaga Pengembangan Komputerisasi Universitas Gunadarma

Depok, Indonesia

#### **Golang Assistant**

Lembaga Pengembangan Komputerisasi Universitas Gunadarma is a college laboratory that developing in skills for college student. As a Golang Asisstant my responsibilities are to:

- Teach Golang programming language.
- Interact with college student as mentor. Check the submission.

# **SKILLS, ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS**

Languages: Fluent in Indonesia; Conversational Proficiency in English; Conversational Proficiency in Arabic.

Technical Skills: (Programming – Golang, C, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Framework ReactJS)

(Non-programming - Adobe Photoshop, Ms. Office, Figma) Interests:

Design UI/UX, Tech, Web Development, Fintech, Start-up.